wedplan.net 2019-02-24

# Privacy Policy - WedFolio

We are committed to providing the highest quality experience for our **clients** and for our **vendors**. With that goal in mind, **WedFolio** was proactively developed with user privacy as a core concern, not as a "bolted-on" afterthought. This document describes the types of data we collect and manage and the ways in which clients and vendors may share information publicly and communicate privately. This document is part of our Terms of Service, and by using **WedFolio** , you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service.

* * *

#### Overview

There are three basic user types associated with our service: anonymous users (unregistered site visitors), **clients** (registered users who are planning their wedding), and **vendors** (registered wedding business users).

The **WedFolio** platform was designed to help clients connect with interested and available wedding service vendors and vice versa. To accomplish this we have created a robust **private** and **public** messaging system. When posting a message on our platform it will be clear whether you are posting a message publicly or you are sending a message to a vendor or client privately. In either case, any personal information you choose to post in any message is at your own discretion.

* * *

#### Messages

  * **Public messages.** At your option you may choose to post messages to the Newsfeed section of our website. Anything you post to the Newsfeed should be considered public information. We encourage clients and vendors to not disclose their contact information or other sensitive information in any public message. Clients and vendors may delete any public message they have posted to the Newsfeed at any time and for any reason by clicking the "delete" button next to the message. 
  * **Private messages.** Clients and vendors may choose to communicate with each other by sending private messages. In such cases, the contact information of the sender is not disclosed to the recipient unless the sender specifically includes that information in the message itself. We encourage clients and vendors to send each other their direct contact information if they are interested in communicating directly — outside of the **WedFolio** platform. 

* * *

#### Actions

  * **Public actions.** Certain actions you may choose to take on the **WedFolio** platform as a client or vendor may be publicly available. This would include actions like posting photos, videos, updates to your public profile, and so forth. For clients, adding a vendor to your "I do's" list is a public action. For vendors, "liking" another vendor is also a public action. These social actions are designed to help clients and vendors better and more effectively interact and network with each other. 
  * **Private actions.** Most of the other actions you may choose to take on the **WedFolio** platform not mentioned in the previous section are private actions. This would include things like sending a private message to a client or vendor. For clients, adding a vendor to your "I don'ts" list is a private action. For vendors, "disliking" another vendor is also a private action. In other words, the vendor in this example would not be made aware of the client's or vendor's private action. 

* * *

#### Information

  * **Public information.** For clients, your public information would include your first name, your partner's first name, your anticipated wedding date, the anticipated location of your wedding, and other public profile information you may choose to provide. For vendors, your public information would include your company name, your company phone number, company description, business location, and other public profile information you may choose to provide. 
  * **Private information.** For clients, private information would include information such as your password. For vendors, private information would include things like your password, User ID, payment history, etc. 

We may share private information you have provided to us, including in cases where:

  * doing so is appropriate to carry out your own request;
  * we believe it's needed to enforce our Terms of Service, or that is legally required;
  * we believe it's needed to detect, prevent or address fraud, security, or technical issues;
  * otherwise protect our property, legal rights, or that of others.

**WedFolio** is operated from the United States. If you are visiting the website from outside the U.S., you agree to any processing of any personal information you provide us according to this policy.

We may contact you by email or other means. For example, we may send you promotional emails relating to **WedFolio** or other third parties we feel you would be interested in, or communicate with you about your use of the **WedFolio** website. We may also use technology to verify if and when you open an email from us or if and when an email we attempt to deliver is undeliverable. These measures are used to improve the quality and timeliness of our service. You can immediately terminate email communications from us by clicking the designated link included in the footer of any email notifications we send to you.

* * *

#### Sensitive Data Transmission and Retention

We employ industry standard techniques to protect against unauthorized access of data about you that we store. On pages where the transmission of sensitive data such as passwords or credit card data is to be transmitted, we secure the transmission to our servers via strong 256-bit SSL encryption. Passwords are strongly hashed for security purposes using industry standard practices. For our protection and for yours, credit card numbers and security codes are never stored on our servers in any manner, including in encrypted or in hashed form.

* * *

#### Other Data Collected

We collect anonymous data from every visitor of the website to monitor traffic and fix bugs. For example, we collect information like web requests, the data sent in response to such requests, the Internet Protocol address, the browser type, the browser language, and a timestamp for the request.

We ask you to "sign up" and "sign in" and to provide certain personal information (such as your name and email address) in order to be able to provide services customized to you. In order to enable these or any other customized features, we use cookies to store session information for your security and for the security of our data. Certain parts of our service may be accessible with cookies blocked or disabled but none of our personalized services can function without cookies being enabled.

You are able to view, change, and remove the data associated with the profile you create. Should you choose to delete your account, you may do this from your account profile page or by making a request at our Support form.

Minors and children should not use **WedFolio**. By using the website, you represent that you have the legal capacity to enter into a binding agreement.

* * *

#### Unauthorized Access

We make every effort to prevent unauthorized access to any and all information that you may submit to our servers. We cannot, however, guarantee that unauthorized access to this information will never occur. In the unlikely event that a breach in site security is determined, we will make every attempt to notify you of the matter. Due to the existing legal regulatory and security environment, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personally indentifiable information will not be disclosed voluntarily or involuntarily to third parties. Under certain circumstances, the government or third parties may lawfully or unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

Additionally, in the unlikely event that we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement, or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. We reserve the right to deny access to any or all features of the site for any reason, including cases where we believe fraud, abuse, misrepresentation, or breach of site policy has been committed by a site visitor.

* * *

#### Change of Control

Should ownership of our business change, your information may be transferred to the new owner so they are able to continue to provide you service.
